Finding aid to the Alexander C. Sanger papers SSC.MS.00654
Sophia Smith Collection
- Speeches, 1959-2016; 3
  - "Completing the unfinished business of Planned Parenthood", 1995 October 23; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Planned Parenthood/Chicago area donor's circle, 1995 October 24; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Introduction of Dr. David Schnarch, 1995 November 4; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - PP Dayton, OH, 1995 November 7; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - "Planned Parenthood values are family values", 1995 November 7; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - "Completing PP's unfinished business," at PP of Omaha, Council Bluffs, 1995 November 15; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - PP of New Mexico, 1995 November 16; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - "Thoughts on the PP Movement", 1995; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Misc speeches, 1995; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Notes for speeches, 1995; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - PP of Dallas, 1996 January 16; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Lobbying Institute, 1996 January 18; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - NYU School of Medicine, 1996 February 20; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - PP of Southwest FL, 1996 March 20; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Nat'l Council of Jewish Women, 1996 March 26; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - PP of South Palm Beach and Broward Counties, 1996 March 29; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Introduction for Robert Klein, 1996 March; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Tulsa Unitarian Church, 1996 April 21; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - PP of Bucks County, 1996 April 22; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - PP of Palm Beach area, 1996 April 22; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Strong Business Group, 1996 April 30; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - "A family gathering", 1996 May 6; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - PP NYC Dinner/MS Award, 1996 May 6; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Testimony before the Senate Democratic Task Force on Health Care in New York State, 1996 May 9; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Nassau Civil Liberties Union, 1996 June 4; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - PP Kalamazoo, 1996 July 9; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - PP of NE Pennsylvania, 1996 September 8; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - PP of Suffolk County, 1996 September 15; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - PP of SE Ohio, 1996 September 17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Eulogy for Mimi Coleman Thompson, 1996 October 7; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - YWCA at Ulster County, 1996 October 18; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Draft speech for Miami, 1996 September 17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - "Sex, Values and Message" PP of East Central IL, 1996 December 11; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - PP NYC press releases, 1996; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Notes for speeches, 1996; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Midland Coalition for Choice, 1997 January 17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - FPA Conference, Albany, NY, 1997 January 21; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - A family gathering event, 1997 May 5; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - PP of East Central MI, 1997 May 8; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - "Medical Abortion in Today's Climate" NY Academy of Medicine, 1997 May 15; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Evelyn Sharp memorial service, 1997 May 20; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - PP of Hawaii, 1997 June 5; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - PP of Central NJ, 1997 June 11; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Expanding Access to Emergency Contraception Conference, NY Academy of Medicine, 1997 September 29; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Robert and Harriet Heilbrunn Center dedication, 1997 October 21; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - PP of Schenectady, "25 Years of Roe", 1997 October 22; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Church/State Luncheon, 1997 December 2; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - "The future of contraception," The Cosmopolitan Club, 1997 December 10; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Al Franken introduction, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Pat Schroeder intro, MS Award, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - "College Version of Emergency Contraception" speech, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - PP NYC/Board/Council re: "merger watch", 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Notes about speeches, 1997; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Mapping the Future of Choice conference, opening and closing remarks, 1998 January 21; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - PP of Orange and Durham counties, NC, 1998 February 4; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - PP of Metropolitan NJ, Inc, 1998 March 10; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "A family gathering", 1998 April 27; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Notes for "Garden Party for PP" of Arkansas, East OK, 1998 May 6; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Virginia league for PP, 1998 May 26; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - PP of West TX 60th Anniversary Galas, 1998 August 12-13; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 2nd annual "Planned Parenthood Votes! Washington" awards luncheon, 1998 September 10; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - PP Reproductive Health Services' 30th anniversary, 1998 October 15; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - PP of Minn/South Dakota, 70th Ann. Galas, 1998 October 23; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Conference on Adolescent Sexual Health, 1998 October 26; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Tribute to Dr. Barnett Slepian, 1998 October 27; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Misc speeches, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Notes for speeches, 1998; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Family Planning Advocates Conference, January 25, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Women's City Club, April 6, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - PP Mar Monte, CA, 1999 April 14 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - PP Orange County, CA, 1999 April 14 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - PP Northern Adirondak, 1999 June 14 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Medical School, 1999 May 5 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - PP Mar Monte Sacramento, CA, 1999 June 30 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - PP St. Louis, 1999 September 22 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Hospital, 1999 October 12 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - PP Southeast Virginia, 1999 October 27 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - American Medical Women's Association, 1999 November 11 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Bronx Lebanon Hospital, 1999 November 19 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - PP Mar Monte Santa Cruz, 1999 November (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Bronx-Lebanon Family Practice, 1999 December 2 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Baruch College, 1999 December 21 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - AFG, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Speech Notes and Statements, 1999 January-March (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Speech Notes and Statements, 1999 March-July (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Speech Notes and Statements, 1999 June (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Speech Notes and Statements, 1999 August-September (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - General, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Volunteer Speech, 2000 January (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - PP Golden Gate, 2000 January (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Brookdale Hospital, 2000 January 19 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Family Planning Advocates, 2000 February 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - PP Iowa, 2000 March 16 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Clinician Training - Columbia Presbyterian, 2000 March 9 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - PP Dallas, 2000 April 7 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "Women, Abortion, & Federalism", 2000 June (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - IPPF, San Fransisco, 2000 June 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Working Assets, San Francisco, 2000 June 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - PP Lubbock, TX, 2000 June 8 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - PP Six Rivers, 2000 June 28 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - PP Rocky Mountains, 2000 August 24 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "Law, Abortion, & Morality", 2000 September 13 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - PP San Diego, 2000 September 14 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Family Planning Association, India, 2000 October 10 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - PP Golden Gate, 2000 October 19 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - PP Hudson Peconic, 2000 November 5 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - PP Nassau County, 2000 November 6 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Rose Ray eulogy, January 6, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - PP New York City Event, 2001 January 16 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - PP Mar Monte, 2001 January 23-27 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - IPPF New York City, 2001 March 8 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - PP Southern New Jersey, 2001 March 14 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Downstate Medical Center, 2001 April 16 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Yale University, 2001 April 17 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - IPPF San Francisco, 2001 April 26 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Accepting Margaret Sanger Awward, 2001 May 10 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Chataqua "Margaret Sanger, the Woman Rebel", 2001 July 17 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - The Margaret Sanger Society / PP Mid-Hudson Valley, 2001 July 24 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - PP Development Officers Council Philadelphia, PA, 2001 August 9 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Remarks to PP Development Officers Council, Philadelphia PA, 2001 August 9 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - PP Los Angeles, 2001 September 12-13 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Tribute to Dr. Irving Rust, 2001 September 14 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - PP of Chester County, PA Community Luncheon, 2001 October 3 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - PP of Chester County Gift Planning Society, 2001 October 3 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - PP of Chester County international Speech, 2001 October 4 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - PP Central PA Annual Meeting, 2001 October 24 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - PP Southeast Michigan Capital Campaign Lunch, 2001 October 25 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - "Saving Women's Lives" U.S. Conference on Women, 2001 November 3 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Nassau County Medical Center, 2001 December 11 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - "Phenomenon of Heroism" & Margaret Sanger Notes / Research, 2001 July 17 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Notes from IPPF meeting, 2001 September 12-16 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - PP Chester County Notes, 2001 October 4 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - "Saving Women's Lives" notes, 2001 October 5 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - PP Southeast Michigan notes, 2001 October (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Iowa Research, 2002 January (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - IPPF - San Francisco notes, 2002 April (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Ohio Research, 2002 May (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut Research, 2002 May (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - South Carolina Research, 2002 January (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Florida Research, 2002 March (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey Research, 2002 April (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - SFPA Conference Research, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Florida Prep/Research, 2002 September (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Wesminster School notes, 2002 December 9 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Misc. PPFA and Politics Notes, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - New York State Research, 2002 May (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Massachusetts Research, 2003 May, September (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - New Jersey Research, 2003 November (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Tennessee Research, 2003 December (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Speech to China Commission on Population, 2009 June 23 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - "The History of Abortion and Roe v. Wade", 2002 January 9 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - PP of South Carolina, 2002 January 23-24 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - IPPF New York City notes / misc., 2002 March 6 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - "United States Population Policy and China" China Family Planning Association, 2002 March 11 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - China Family Planning Association notes / misc., 2002 March 11 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - PP Sarasota Florida, 2002 March 18 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Princeton University, 2002 April 9 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - PP Middle Tennessee, 2002 May 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Religion and Government" PP of Middle Tennessee, 2002 May 3 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - PP Greater Iowa, 2002 May 11 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - PP Connecticut, 2002 May 16 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - PP Mahoning Valley Youngstown, OH, 2002 May 20 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - PP Cleveland, 2002 May 22 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - SFPA Speech, Washington D.C., 2002 June 18 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - PP of Greater Orlando, 2002 September 26 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - SUNY New Paltz, 2003 April 24 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - PP Syracuse / Rochester, 2003 June 5 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - "PPFA and Sex, a Lasting Relationship" PPFA Central Region meetings, 2003 September 13 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - PPFA Central Region: PPFA + Sex Speech, 2003 September 13 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - PP Central Region, 2003 September 14 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - PP League of MA at Smith College, 2003 September 15 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - PPFA Eastern Regional Meeting, 2003 October 25 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - PP Mercer Area, 2003 November 5 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - IPPF San Francisco, 2003 November 17 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - "Margaret Sanger, the Woman Rebel" Westminster School, 2003 December 9 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - IPPF/WHR Board Speech on Development, 2005 December 4 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Presentation of IPPF/WHR Medal of Honor to the family of George Tiller, M.D., 2009 September 25 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Tribute to Jim Sligar, 2010 December 10 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - IPPF / Profamilia Event at home of Suzanne Sunshine, 2001 January 19 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - SUNY New Paltz Lecture, 2010 September 29 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - "Brief History of Reproductive Rights Movement", 2010 October 17 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - PP Rhode Island Press Conference, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - "The Proper Role of Government: A Case Study of Partial Birth Abortions", undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Alexander Sanger Speech, 2006-2016; B (Box 99)
    - UCSD Environmental Seminar Series, March 24th, 2014 (Box 99)
    - Santa Fe, January 26-27, 2016
- Writings and Interviews, 1970-2016; 4
  This series contains articles by Alexander Sanger, research, interviews of A.S., letters to the editor, work on "Beyond Choice", and book tour writings and speeches.
  - Book Tour writings, speeches, A
    - Beyond Choice book proposal, 1994-1995; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Public Affairs misc materials, 2001-2005; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Book tour inquiries, 2003-2005; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Marketing, op-eds, 2004; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Marketing, opinion leaders, 2003-2004; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Marketing material, 2004; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Foreign book tour, 2004; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Goldberg McDuffie publicity, 2004; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Carol Fitzgerald - Book Report Network, 2004-2006; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Speech notes, 2003-2005; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Speech talking points, 2004-2005; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Book reviews, 2004-2005; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Misc news features, 2004 January-October; 8 folders (8 folders) (Box 22, Folder 4-11)
    - The O'Reilly Factor, 2004 January 20; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - PP Phoenix, 2004 January 23; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Lenox Hill Bookstore, 2004 February 2; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Colony Club, 2004 February 17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Washington, DC, 2004 February 17-18; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Seattle, 2004 February 21-24; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - San Francisco, 2004 February 24-27; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - PP Corning, NY, 2004 February; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Los Angeles, 2004 February-March; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - San Diego, 2004 March 4-6; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - PP Action Council Dinner, Salt Lake City, 2004 March 6; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - NYU, 2004 March 9; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Boston, 2004 March 10; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Rhode Island, 2004 March 11; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Florida, 2004 March 15; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Vermont, 2004 March 28; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Bellingham, WA, 2004 March 30-31; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Idaho, 2004 April 1-2; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Alabama, 2004 April 7; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - New York, Jackie Weld party, 2004 April 8; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Connecticut, 2004 April 18; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Houston, 2004 April 19; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Princeton, 2004 April 21; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Portland, OR, 2004 April 16; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Kentucky, 2004 April 12; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - SUNY New Paltz, 2004 April 22; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Texas, 2004 April 27-29; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Delaware, 2004 May 11; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ohio, 2004 May 12; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota, 2004 May 13; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - NYC - All Souls, 2004 May 16; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - PP of Central NJ, 2004 May 17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Kansas City, 2004 May 18; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - New Mexico, 2004 May 19; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Richland, WA, 2004 May 20; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Flint, MI, 2004 May 21; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - California, 2004 May 26; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Princeton reunion, 2004 May 28; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Massachusetts - Brookline House Party, 2004 June 1; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Marymount College, NYC, 2004 June 10; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - PP NYC, 2004 June 8; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Spokane, WA, 2004 July 22; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Long Island, 2004 July 24; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Millbrook, NY, 2004 August 7; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Development Officers Retreat, 2004 August 9; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Kansas City, Dr. Tiller Event, 2004 August 12; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Hawaii, 2004 September 12; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Dallas, 2004 September 16; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - NCJW Westbury, 2004 September 21; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Flint, MI, 2004 September 27; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Kalamazoo, MI, 2004 September 29; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Niagara, 2004 September 30; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Harrisburg, PA, 2004 October 1; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - North Carolina, 2004 October 13; 2 folders (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 11, 12)
    - Charlottesville, VA, 2004 October 16; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - PP NE Pennsylvania, 2004 October 18; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Worcester, MA, 2004 October 19; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Camden, NJ, 2004 October 20; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Los Angeles, WRRAP, 2004 October 27; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Kentucky ACLU, 2004 October 28; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Johns Hopkins, 2004 November 4; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Hudson - Peconic, 2004 November 7-9; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Miami Book Fair, 2004 November 10-14; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Toledo, 2004 November 17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Dayton, OH, 2004 November 19; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Andover, MA, 2004 November 20; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Pasadena, 2004 November 29; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Oklahoma, 2004 December 1; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Tennessee, 2004 December 6-7; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Publisher's Weekly, 2004 December 22; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Beyond Choice paperback and hardcover books, 2004; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ACS personal schedule, 2004 January-March; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ACS personal schedule, 2004 March-November; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Various speeches, 2004-2005; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Various features in newspapers and websites, 2005; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Spring Island, SC, 2005 February 15; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - "Reclaiming the Forbidden Fruit," Portland, OR, 2005 March 16-17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Annual Spring Educ. Luncheon, Amarillo, TX, 2005 April 26; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Rubin Museum of Art, 2005 May 19; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Northern MI, 2005 June; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Beyond Choice, Bedford, NY, 2005 June 5; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Santa Barbara, Mar Monte, 2005 June 27; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Denver, CO, 2005 July 15; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Oklahoma City, 2005 September 15; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Champaign, IL, 2005 September 22; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Wisconsin 70th Anniversary, 2005 October 19; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Bucks County, PA, 2005 October 25; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Phillips Academy, Andover, 2007 February 23; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - PPGNNJ - Englewood, NJ, 2007 June 6; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - PP Southern NJ, 2007 October 25; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - PPGNNJ - Morristown, 2008 April 16; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - PPGGNJ - Fort Lee, 2008 November 5; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Jackson Hole, WY, 2006 August 14; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - North Haven, ME, 2006 August 17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ME Lobster Research, 2006 August 17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Brandeis speech in NJ, 2006 April 27; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Las Vegas, 2006 September 14; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - PP NE Pennsylvania, 2006 September 17; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Interview, B
    - Interview, Mainichi, 2009; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Interview, Radio New Zealand, 2010 May; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - South Dakota, South Dakota Movie Produced, 2013 (Box 99)
    - Joan Garry Interview, 2013 April 4 (Box 99)
    - Planned Parenthood of America Oral History Project, 2014 October 12 (Box 99)
    - Ascent of Women, 2014 November 24 (Box 99)
  - Research, C
    - News Articles and Blogposts by others, 2013-2016, 1981; 2013-2016 (Box 99)
    - Negative Margaret Sanger Stories, undated (Box 99)
    - Ms - News Footage Research, undated (Box 99)
  - Writings by Alexander Sanger, D
    - Articles by Alexander Sanger, 2007-2016 (Box 99)